All right, you're done. There were a lot of new things that time. But, afterall,
you're becoming a seasoned Android programmer by now.
As I mentioned before, we're going to use NotificationCompat.Builder
to build our notification. It's easy to build
a nice looking notification that has our icon
representing the weather forecast, the title for our
App. And our content text, the forecast with
highs and lows. We're going to use another class
from the support library, to create a task stack builder
for our pending intent. This is a simple case
of task stack builder, because all we have is a
single item on our stack. We just add the
next intent and use it to build out pending intent
that we pass into the notification manager. Finally we call
the notification manager with the built intent from our builder,
with a notify function. One of the great things about notification manager is
it can be used from any thread even though it is displaying UI.